Finding Aid for Ben East papers, 1935-1980
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - Miscellaneous
    - Predators and Poisoning, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Radio Game Tracking, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Snakes (Box 13)
    - Travel Article
      - Spring 1975 (Box 13)
      - Summer 1978 (Box 13)
      - October, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Unharvested Game (Box 13)